Cuneiform Tablet Collection
Cuneiform Tablet Collection
- Cuneiform tablets
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 220 (CDLI 167), circa 2100-2000; delivery of sieves (Box 12)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 221 (CDLI 318), circa 2100-2000; delivery of lambs (Box 12)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 222 (CDLI 319), circa 2100-2000; delivery of lambs (Box 12)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 223 (CDLI 457), circa 2100-2000; bricks (Box 12)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 224 (CDLI 456), circa 2100-2000; [damaged] (Box 12)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 225 (CDLI 317), circa 2100-2000; management of livestock (Box 12)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 226 (CDLI 321), circa 2100-2000; delivery of livestock (Box 12)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 227 (CDLI 409), circa 2100-2000; road provisions (Box 12)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 228 (CDLI 360), circa 2100-2000; rations of barley and cloths for weavers (Box 12)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 229 (CDLI 465), circa 2100-2000; reed (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 230 (CDLI 3), circa 2100-2000; workers for loading and unloading boats (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 231 (CDLI 188), circa 2100-2000; receipt for wood (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 232 (CDLI 420), circa 2100-2000; delivery of knives (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 233 (CDLI 395), circa 2100-2000; tax on date palms (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 234 (CDLI 66), circa 2100-2000; workers for field work (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 235 (CDLI 424), circa 2100-2000; list of persons (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 236 (CDLI 21), circa 2100-2000; workers for transporting reed to the depot (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 237 (CDLI 426), circa 2100-2000; remuneration for workers (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 238 (CDLI 135), circa 2100-2000; two sick people (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 239 (CDLI 233), circa 2100-2000; workers for the threshing of barley (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 240 (CDLI 67), circa 2100-2000; workers for harvest work (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 241 (CDLI 462), circa 2100-2000; monthly provisions (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 242 (CDLI 472), circa 2100-2000; proper names (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 243 (CDLI 221), circa 2100-2000; receipt for reed objects (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 244 (CDLI 285), circa 2100-2000; receipt for seeds (Box 13)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 245 (CDLI 314), circa 2100-2000; workers for picking up barley (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 246 (CDLI 286), circa 2100-2000; receipt for birds (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 247 (CDLI 79), circa 2100-2000; receipt for glue for tablets (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 248 (CDLI 16), circa 2100-2000; delivery of sesame (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 249 (CDLI 191), circa 2100-2000; workers for threshing (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 250 (CDLI 163), circa 2100-2000; receipt for rations of barley for sailors (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 251 (CDLI 436), circa 2100-2000; rations of bread and bran (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 252 (CDLI 205), circa 2100-2000; workers for carrying straw (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 253 (CDLI 19), circa 2100-2000; workers for transporting reed by boat (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 254 (CDLI 165), circa 2100-2000; inspection of navigation crews (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 255 (CDLI 160), circa 2100-2000; work time for the transport of barley by ship (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 256 (CDLI 240), circa 2100-2000; harvest work (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 257 (CDLI 32), circa 2100-2000; workers for irrigation work (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 258 (CDLI 284), circa 2100-2000; delivery of reed bundles (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 259 (CDLI 422), circa 2100-2000; list of persons (Box 14)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 260 (CDLI 431), circa 2100-2000; delivery of barley (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 261 (CDLI 419), circa 2100-2000; delivery of sickles (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 262 (CDLI 81), circa 2100-2000; plowmen for the irrigation of fields (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 263 (CDLI 193), circa 2100-2000; workers for carrying reeds under the command of Niurum (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 264 (CDLI 128), circa 2100-2000; bread transported by boat (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 265 (CDLI 33), circa 2100-2000; workers for cutting ? and transporting reed (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 266 (CDLI 287), circa 2100-2000; receipt for reed bundles for the Emaš (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 267 (CDLI 211), circa 2100-2000; women for a kašdea (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 268 (CDLI 272), circa 2100-2000; receipt for wood for the construction of boats (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 269 (CDLI 109), circa 2100-2000; workers for towing a rented boat (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 270 (CDLI 138), circa 2100-2000; workers and menials for irrigation work (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 271 (CDLI 4), circa 2100-2000; deepening work on a basin (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 272 (CDLI 446), circa 2100-2000; flour (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 273 (CDLI 51), circa 2100-2000; workers for harvest work (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 274 (CDLI 288), circa 2100-2000; reed bundles for the Erendur depot (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 275 (CDLI 119), circa 2100-2000; weavers for erecting mill stones (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 276 (CDLI 475), circa 2100-2000; ? (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 277 (CDLI 388), circa 2100-2000; barley for livestock (Box 15)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 278 (CDLI 425), circa 2100-2000; women and men for irrigation (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 279 (CDLI 432), circa 2100-2000; receipt for an object (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 280 (CDLI 182), circa 2100-2000; receipt for sheep (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 281 (CDLI 397), circa 2100-2000; delivery of wool (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 282 (CDLI 410), circa 2100-2000; road provisions (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 283 (CDLI 69), circa 2100-2000; workers for field work (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 284 (CDLI 261), circa 2100-2000; workers for the transport and storage of barley (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 285 (CDLI 227), circa 2100-2000; receipt for reed bundles cut and stocked (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 286 (CDLI 416), circa 2100-2000; money for dates (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 287 (CDLI 149), circa 2100-2000; workers hired for irrigation work (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 288 (CDLI 98), circa 2100-2000; delivery of reeds (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 289 (CDLI 357), circa 2100-2000; leather objects (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 290 (CDLI 59), circa 2100-2000; two dead men (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 291 (CDLI 279), circa 2100-2000; levy of dead livestock (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 292 (CDLI 249), circa 2100-2000; receipt for hides (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 293 (CDLI 127), circa 2100-2000; receipt for dogwood branches (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 294 (CDLI 17), circa 2100-2000; delivery of sesame (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 295 (CDLI 355), circa 2100-2000; receipt for leather bags for two kianag (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 296 (CDLI 26), circa 2100-2000; receipt for hides (Box 16)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 297 (CDLI 132), circa 2100-2000; receipt for leather bags (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 298 (CDLI 190), circa 2100-2000; receipt for bitumen (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 299 (CDLI 214), circa 2100-2000; workers for transporting tablets (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 300 (CDLI 210), circa 2100-2000; care for small livestock (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 301 (CDLI 315), circa 2100-2000; workers stationed at a marsa (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 302 (CDLI 307), circa 2100-2000; receipt for hides (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 303 (CDLI 312), circa 2100-2000; delivery of reed bundles for the palace (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 304 (CDLI 11), circa 2100-2000; reed baskets and mats (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 305 (CDLI 96), circa 2100-2000; receipt for reeds (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 306 (CDLI 92), circa 2100-2000; workers for irrigation and field work (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 307 (CDLI 130), circa 2100-2000; receipt for reeds (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 308 (CDLI 237), circa 2100-2000; workers for irrigation work (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 309 (CDLI 229), circa 2100-2000; workers for field work (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 310 (CDLI 380), circa 2100-2000; barley (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 311 (CDLI 445), circa 2100-2000; delivery of flour (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 312 (CDLI 379), circa 2100-2000; delivery of barley (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 313 (CDLI 447), circa 2100-2000; delivery of flour (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 314 (CDLI 15), circa 2100-2000; workers for cleaning a basin and cutting grass (Box 17)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 315 (CDLI 413), circa 2100-2000; money (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 316 (CDLI 328), circa 2100-2000; management of livestock (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 317 (CDLI 311), circa 2100-2000; delivery of pickaxes (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 318 (CDLI 386), circa 2100-2000; delivery of barley (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 319 (CDLI 443), circa 2100-2000; flower, sattukku (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 320 (CDLI 330), circa 2100-2000; taking care of a young dead animal (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 321 (CDLI 331), circa 2100-2000; price for two donkeys (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 322 (CDLI 333), circa 2100-2000; delivery of oxen (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 323 (CDLI 327), circa 2100-2000; rations of barley for livestock (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 324 (CDLI 437), circa 2100-2000; workers for carrying bricks (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 325 (CDLI 335), circa 2100-2000; levy of small livestock (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 326 (CDLI 329), circa 2100-2000; management of small livestock (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 327 (CDLI 415), circa 2100-2000; delivery of thread (šà-gu) (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 328 (CDLI 417), circa 2100-2000; money for spices (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 329 (CDLI 377), circa 2100-2000; ration of barley (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 330 (CDLI 336), circa 2100-2000; delivery of small livestock (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 331 (CDLI 332), circa 2100-2000; management of donkeys (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 332 (CDLI 384), circa 2100-2000; barley (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 333 (CDLI 471), circa 2100-2000; delivery of flour? (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 334 (CDLI 474), circa 2100-2000; delivery of reed, bitumen, etc. (Box 18)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 335 (CDLI 467), circa 2100-2000; [clay tablet damaged, no content given] (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 336 (CDLI 414), circa 2100-2000; balance of bills for copper (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 337 (CDLI 433), circa 2100-2000; basket for tablets (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 338 (CDLI 448), circa 2100-2000; delivery of oil (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 339 (CDLI 375), circa 2100-2000; delivery of barley for cattle (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 340 (CDLI 382), circa 2100-2000; barley, food for sheep (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 341 (CDLI 343), circa 2100-2000; delivery of a donkey (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 342 (CDLI 154), circa 2100-2000; delivery of harnesses (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 343 (CDLI 209), circa 2100-2000; management of livestock (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 344 (CDLI 243), circa 2100-2000; receipt for leather bottles (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 345 (CDLI 427), circa 2100-2000; delivery of reed (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 346 (CDLI 49), circa 2100-2000; woman in the service of Dagumu (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 347 (CDLI 406), circa 2100-2000; receipt for cloths (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 348 (CDLI 362), circa 2100-2000; delivery of barley (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 349 (CDLI 364), circa 2100-2000; delivery of barley, wheat and flour (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 350 (CDLI 337), circa 2100-2000; delivery of livestock (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 351 (CDLI 340), circa 2100-2000; receipt for small livestock (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 352 (CDLI 111), circa 2100-2000; receipt for leather for a delivery of plows (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 353 (CDLI 91), circa 2100-2000; arrear delivery of reeds from the account of Inimgina (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 354 (CDLI 449), circa 2100-2000; reeds on account (Box 19)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 355 (CDLI 86), circa 2100-2000; receipt for sheep (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 356 (CDLI 84), circa 2100-2000; delivery of flour (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 357 (CDLI 142), circa 2100-2000; workers for irrigation (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 358 (CDLI 255), circa 2100-2000; receipt for products of agriculture (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 359 (CDLI 352), circa 2100-2000; dead animals (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 360 (CDLI 353), circa 2100-2000; levy of sandals (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 361 (CDLI 454), circa 2100-2000; tablet: "no delivery" (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 362 (CDLI 361), circa 2100-2000; barley, wage arrears (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 363 (CDLI 230), circa 2100-2000; delivery of reed bundles (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 364 (CDLI 345), circa 2100-2000; receipt for small livestock (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 365 (CDLI 196), circa 2100-2000; inspection of workers for field work and for the guard (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 366 (CDLI 224), circa 2100-2000; workers for working in the depot (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 367 (CDLI 76), circa 2100-2000; workers for the harvest (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 368 (CDLI 299), circa 2100-2000; receipt for reed mats for boats loaded with flour (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 369 (CDLI 136), circa 2100-2000; delivery of hides (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 370 (CDLI 52), circa 2100-2000; workers for irrigation works (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 371 (CDLI 440), circa 2100-2000; workers for working at the silos (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 372 (CDLI 350), circa 2100-2000; levy of small livestock (Box 20)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 373 (CDLI 293), circa 2100-2000; irrigation work to reduce water flooding (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 374 (CDLI 246), circa 2100-2000; workers for the harvest (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 375 (CDLI 115), circa 2100-2000; workers for irrigation work; damaged (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 376 (CDLI 313), circa 2100-2000; metal objects (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 377 (CDLI 121), circa 2100-2000; workers for irrigation work (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 378 (CDLI 242), circa 2100-2000; receipt for reed objects (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 379 (CDLI 348), circa 2100-2000; care for an old cow (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 380 (CDLI 131), circa 2100-2000; receipt for a leather bag (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 381 (CDLI 442), circa 2100-2000; workers for bringing a boat to Daga (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 382 (CDLI 5), circa 2100-2000; workers from a workshop in Gaeš (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 383 (CDLI 439), circa 2100-2000; menials for carrying straw (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 384 (CDLI 39), circa 2100-2000; receipt for leather for [an] oxen [harness?] (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 385 (CDLI 56), circa 2100-2000; workers for irrigation work (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 386 (CDLI 22), circa 2100-2000; receipt for leather objects for a harness and whips (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 387 (CDLI 264), circa 2100-2000; receipt for hides (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 388 (CDLI 316), circa 2100-2000; barley and bran for small livestock (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 389 (CDLI 367), circa 2100-2000; delivery of barley (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 390 (CDLI 173), circa 2100-2000; receipt for wood for the depot (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 391 (CDLI 435), circa 2100-2000; care for workers (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 392 (CDLI 267), circa 2100-2000; receipt for reed bundles (Box 21)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 393 (CDLI 207), circa 2100-2000; irrigation work (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 394 (CDLI 347), circa 2100-2000; closure of livestock accounts (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 395 (CDLI 186), circa 2100-2000; delivery of bran (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 396 (CDLI 71), circa 2100-2000; receipt for reed mats (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 397 (CDLI 201), circa 2100-2000; delivery of oil (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 398 (CDLI 202), circa 2100-2000; management of lambs (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 399 (CDLI 70), circa 2100-2000; women for irrigation control (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 400 (CDLI 273), circa 2100-2000; workers for the harvest and irrigation (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 401 (CDLI 151), circa 2100-2000; workers for the cutting of reeds (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 402 (CDLI 238), circa 2100-2000; irrigation work (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 403 (CDLI 112), circa 2100-2000; workers for setting up millstones (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 404 (CDLI 144), circa 2100-2000; workers for field work (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 405 (CDLI 444), circa 2100-2000; delivery of flour, wool, bitumen (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 406 (CDLI 281), circa 2100-2000; levy of small livestock (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 407 (CDLI 274), circa 2100-2000; workers for transporting reed (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 408 (CDLI 342), circa 2100-2000; management of livestock (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 409 (CDLI 344), circa 2100-2000; delivery of small livestock (Box 22)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 410 (CDLI 280), circa 2100-2000; levy of livestock (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 411 (CDLI 378), circa 2100-2000; barley (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 412 (CDLI 146), circa 2100-2000; workers for field work (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 413 (CDLI 263), circa 2100-2000; delivery of small livestock (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 414 (CDLI 117), circa 2100-2000; workers for the harvest (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 415 (CDLI 73), circa 2100-2000; levy of a deer (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 416 (CDLI 373), circa 2100-2000; rations of orgěgidda (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 417 (CDLI 451), circa 2100-2000; label of a tablet basket (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 418 (CDLI 460), circa 2100-2000; flour (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 419 (CDLI 411), circa 2100-2000; beer and bread (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 420 (CDLI 226), circa 2100-2000; field work (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 421 (CDLI 38), circa 2100-2000; workers for the transport of barley per boat (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 422 (CDLI 356), circa 2100-2000; receipt for hides (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 423 (CDLI 464), circa 2100-2000; barley, spelt and wheat for multiple people (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 424 (CDLI 48), circa 2100-2000; soldiers ? for cutting and transporting reed (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 425 (CDLI 403), circa 2100-2000; levy of cloths (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 426 (CDLI 458), circa 2100-2000; delivery of peas and barley (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 427 (CDLI 461), circa 2100-2000; bread for different persons (Box 23)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 428 (CDLI 277), circa 2100-2000; levy of livestock (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 429 (CDLI 282), circa 2100-2000; levy of livestock (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 430 (CDLI 174), circa 2100-2000; receipt for bitumen (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 431 (CDLI 175), circa 2100-2000; receipt for reed bundles (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 432 (CDLI 161), circa 2100-2000; workers for navigation (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 433 (CDLI 338), circa 2100-2000; levy of small livestock for a sattuku (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 434 (CDLI 339), circa 2100-2000; delivery of small livestock (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 435 (CDLI 341), circa 2100-2000; management of sheep (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 436 (CDLI 141), circa 2100-2000; workers for the harvest (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 437 (CDLI 195), circa 2100-2000; receipt for bran (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 438 (CDLI 244), circa 2100-2000; reed object (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 439 (CDLI 18), circa 2100-2000; receipt for money owed by fishermen (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 440 (CDLI 126), circa 2100-2000; grass cut by the herdsmen (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 441 (CDLI 180), circa 2100-2000; workers for irrigation (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 442 (CDLI 468), circa 2100-2000; delivery of products for leather work (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 443 (CDLI 470), circa 2100-2000; delivery of garlic (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 444 (CDLI 400), circa 2100-2000; wool (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 445 (CDLI 28), circa 2100-2000; irrigation work executed by the herdsmen (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 446 (CDLI 72), circa 2100-2000; workers managing an irrigation basin (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 447 (CDLI 129), circa 2100-2000; workers for building silos (Box 24)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 448 (CDLI 152), circa 2100-2000; workers for irrigation work (Box 25)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 449 (CDLI 349), circa 2100-2000; receipt for livestock and wool (Box 25)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 450 (CDLI 54), circa 2100-2000; workers for cutting reed and picking (Box 25)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 451 (CDLI 257), circa 2100-2000; workers for work in the fields and on irrigation (Box 25)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 452 (CDLI 258), circa 2100-2000; workers for transporting barley to Nippur (Box 25)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 453 (CDLI 351), circa 2100-2000; price of animals (Box 25)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 454 (CDLI 423), circa 2100-2000; list of workers (Box 25)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 455 (CDLI 434), circa 2100-2000; delivery of reed and wood (Box 25)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 456 (CDLI 374), circa 2100-2000; ration of barley for workers (Box 25)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 457 (CDLI 166), circa 2100-2000; inspection of maintenance work crews (Box 25)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 458 (CDLI 259), circa 2100-2000; workers for loading a boat (Box 25)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 459 (CDLI 402), circa 2100-2000; levy of cloths (Box 25)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 460 (CDLI 371), circa 2100-2000; arrear of barley (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 461 (CDLI 116), circa 2100-2000; workers for irrigation work (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 462 (CDLI 394), circa 2100-2000; tax on date palms (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 463 (CDLI 254), circa 2100-2000; receipt for baskets (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 464 (CDLI 346), circa 2100-2000; livestock account (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 465 (CDLI 1), circa 2100-2000; reed harvest (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 466 (CDLI 156), circa 2100-2000; workers harvesting palm fibers (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 467 (CDLI 139), circa 2100-2000; receipt for reed baskets (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 468 (CDLI 213), circa 2100-2000; receipt for tablet glue (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 469 (CDLI 241), circa 2100-2000; workers for the harvest (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 470 (CDLI 408), circa 2100-2000; road provisions (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 471 (CDLI 183), circa 2100-2000; receipt for dead goat (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 472 (CDLI 25), circa 2100-2000; receipt for flour, fat, and colorant (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 473 (CDLI 358), circa 2100-2000; cattle given in the custody of different workers (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 474 (CDLI 407), circa 2100-2000; road provisions (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 475 (CDLI 463), circa 2100-2000; money for purchasing oil (Box 26)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 476 (CDLI 469), circa 2100-2000; delivery (Box 27)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 477 (CDLI 369), circa 2100-2000; arrears of barley, receipts (Box 27)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 478 (CDLI 37), circa 2100-2000; workers for the transport of barley per boat (Box 27)